{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_C._Clarke",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/2001:_A_Space_Odyssey",
    "human_readable": "Arthur C. Clarke's notable work is 2001: A Space Odyssey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6194793581962585,
            "question": "What is Arthur C. Clarke most famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5865204334259033,
            "question": "What type of technology plays a central role in '2001: A Space Odyssey'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.579155445098877,
            "question": "What year was the film adaptation of  '2001: A Space Odyssey' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46932730078697205,
            "question": "Which classic film features a story by Arthur C. Clarke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46035757660865784,
            "question": "What is the name of the sentient computer in '2001: A Space Odyssey'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45445477962493896,
            "question": "Besides writing, what else was Arthur C. Clarke known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43069010972976685,
            "question": "Name a science fiction work by Arthur C. Clarke."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2212061583995819,
            "question": "What genre of literature is associated with Arthur C. Clarke's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11925285309553146,
            "question": "Which iconic film sequence features a monolith in space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02016480639576912,
            "question": "Which story explores themes of artificial intelligence and human evolution?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur C. Clarke's notable work is 2001: A Space Odyssey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8027_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which iconic film sequence features a monolith in space?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8027_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of literature is associated with Arthur C. Clarke's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8027_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a science fiction work by Arthur C. Clarke.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8027_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8027_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this statement, as all three files mention Arthur C. Clarke and his notable work, \"2001: A Space Odyssey\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Arthur C. Clarke's notable work is 2001: A Space Odyssey,\" as multiple documents mention this novel, including its significance in the field of science fiction and its collaboration with Stanley Kubrick."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}